moonastro.com 2017-06-06

# MoonAstro.com : Privacy Policy of MoonAstro

**Privacy Policy for www.moonastro.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@moonastro.com.

At www.moonastro.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.moonastro.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.moonastro.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

We are MoonAsto provides astrology services for free. We created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. We understand the importance of feeling safe online and want you to feel comfortable using our personalized services and exchanging information on our web site. We are committed to protecting your personal information and will take reasonable steps to see that this privacy policy is followed within our company. 

**Information that we collect**  
In order to provide you astrology services we may ask you to register and establish your personal profile. During the registration process we may ask you for information such as your name, gender, birth information, e-mail address, password, birth place, etc. This information is used to calculate an accurate horoscope or biorhythm and to provide you with the best possible personalized service. Your e-mail address together with a password is used to secure your profile and to make our personalized e-mail services available to you. We collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities on our site through your IP address or most-recently-visited URL. We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, and to track trends and statistics. 

**Use of information**  
Demographic and profile data, as well as your registration data (i.e., e-mail address, gender, and password) is used to personalize our service to your interests and to deliver personalized information to you. For example, we may decide to use personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information for internal marketing purposes, for trend analysis, to better understand patterns of usage, and for site administration. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can (and you authorize us to do so) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. In instances where we ask for your personally identifiable information and you are notified that the information we are collecting on that page will be shared with third parties, and in cases where you opt-in to share your information with third parties, those disclosures and opt-ins will override anything to the contrary in this privacy policy. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.moonastro.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.moonastro.com. .:: google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.moonastro.com and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.moonastro.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.moonastro.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.moonastro.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us at _[admin@moonastro.com](mailto:admin@moonastro.com)_
